Guide to the Ithaca pamphlet collection, 1863-1915.
Ithaca pamphlet collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Ithaca pamphlet collection, 1863-1915.
5135D
7 volumes.
Printed material, publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Pamphlets, circulars, legal documents, and leaflets documenting various aspects of life and thought in Ithaca, New York.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Pamphlets, circulars, legal documents, and leaflets documenting various aspects of life and thought in Ithaca, New York. Included are lectures and speeches by Cornell University faculty; reports of or to Ithaca city officials and departments such as the Fire Department; pamphlets on the history, principles, and services of local churches, including the First Congregational Church, First Unitarian Church (also known as the First Unitarian Society) and First Presbyterian Church; early telephone directories; constitutions, reports, and manuals of local organizations, such as the Country Club of Ithaca and the Young Men's Christian Association; and illustrated "Carrier's address" booklets of light poetry delivered to subscribers annually by carriers of the Ithaca daily journal. Also included is an early pamphlet written in defense of Cornell University, titled The Cornell University: what it is, and what it is not (1872).
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Country Club of Ithaca (Ithaca, N.Y.); First Congregational Church (Ithaca, N.Y.); First Presbyterian Church (Ithaca, N.Y.); First Unitarian Church (Ithaca, N.Y.); Ithaca (N.Y.). Fire Department.; Young Men's Christian Association (Ithaca, N.Y.)
Titles:
Ithaca daily journal.
Places:
Ithaca (N.Y.); Ithaca (N.Y.); Ithaca (N.Y.) -- Social life and customs.; Ithaca (N.Y.) -- Intellectual life.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- "Annual Report of the Chief Engineer of the Ithaca Fire Department" for 1868, "Together with the Fire Laws of the Village of Ithaca and an Early History of Ithaca, by Horace King, Esq.", 1869; 1; no. 1
- "Fourteenth Annual Report of the Chief Engineer of the Ithaca Fire Department" for 1873, "Together with the Act of Incorporation and Fire Laws", 1873; 1; no. 2
- "Sixteenth Annual Report of the Chief Engineer of the Ithaca Fire Department" for 1875, "Together with the Act of Incorporation and Fire Laws, and Ordinances Relating to the Fire Department and Fires", 1875; 1; no. 3
- "Ithaca Academy Annual Catalogue, 1873-1874", 1873; 1; no. 4
- "An Address Delivered before the Tompkins County Agricultural and Horticultural Society on October 1, 1863, by Hon. Alfred Wells; also, an Address Delivered before the Same Society on September 22, 1859, by Hon. E.J. Richardson", 1863; 1; no. 5
- Tompkins County Agricultural and Horticultural Society list of premiums and regulations of the 49th Annual Fair, 1888; 1; no. 6
- "'The Relations between America and England,' an Address Delivered before the Citizens of Ithaca, by Goldwin Smith, May 19, 1869", 1869; 1; no. 7
- "'History and Topography of New York,' a Lecture, by Horatio Seymour, at Cornell University, June 30, 1870", 1870; 1; no. 8
- "'The Life and Services of Ezra Cornell,'" an Address Delivered at Cornell University on Founder's Day (January 11, 1887), by Francis M. Finch", 1887; 1; no. 9
- "'The Glory of Youth,'" the Baccalaureate Sermon Delivered by Rev. Henry W. Bellows, D.D., before the Graduating Class at Cornell University and Antioch College, June, 1878", 1878; 1; no. 10
- "Cornell University Annual Circular, 1875-1876", 1875; 1; no. 11
- "Cornell University: What It Is and What It Is Not", 1872; 1; no. 12
- "'The Cornell Reprint: Essay on Decision of Character,' by John Foster", 1872; 1; no. 13
- Good Friday services program, "April 19th, 1889, at the Congregational Church of St. Augustine, Commandery, no. 38, Knights Templar, Stationed at Ithaca, N.Y.", 1889; 1; no. 14
- "A Manual of the First Congregational Church of Ithaca, N.Y., Containing Catalogues of Officers and Members, Articles of Faith and Covenants, Rules, etc.", 1887; 1; no. 15
- "Public Worship of the First Congregational Church, of Ithaca, N.Y.", [n.d.]; 1; no. 16
- "History of the First Unitarian Society of Ithaca, by Henry C. Badger, Pastor", 1881; 1; no. 17
- "Directory of the First Methodist Episcopal Church, Ithaca, New York", Dec., 1892; 1; no. 18
- "Tompkins County Calendar for the Circuit Court, Commencing Monday, March 6, 1893", 1893; 1; no. 19
- "Executor's Sale, McGraw Fiske Estate, at Ithaca, N.Y., February 19th, 1891", 1891; 1; no. 20
- "Art Loan Association at First Baptist Church, Ithaca, N.Y.", [n.d.]; 1; no. 21
- Farmer's Almanac for 1891, 1891; 1; no. 22
- "Ithaca Daily Journal, Carrier Boys' Annual Greeting, 1894", 1894; 1; no. 23
- "Direction for Use of the Paster Ballots," concerning, in particular, Clinton D. Bouton [two copies], [n.d.]; 1; no. 24
- Circular from the "Democratic Committee of Fifty" addressed "To the Voters of New York State" concerning the protest of Isaac H. Maynard's nomination to the position of Judge of the Court of Appeals, Nov., 1893; 1; no. 25
- Circular from the "County Anti-Saloon Association" addressed "To the Voters of Tompkins County" concerning the significance of making a "Citizens' Ticket", [n.d.]; 1; no. 26
- "Retail Price List Issued by the Tompkins Co. Druggist Association for Patent Medicines, etc.", Sep., 1886; 1; no. 27
- "Report on Plans for Sewering and Draining the City of Ithaca, N.Y., Made to the Board of Sewer Commissioners, August 30, 1894, by Rudolph Hering, Civil Engineer", 1894; 1; no. 28
- "Statement of Claim: In the Matter of the Claim of Francis M. Finch, Assignee of Ebenezer T. Turner," presented "Before the Board of Canal Appraisers", [n.d.]; 1; no. 29
- "The Blue Ribbon: an Operetta" published in part with "Ithaca Daily Journal, Carrier Boys' Annual Greeting, 1896", 1896; 2; no. 1
- "Ithaca Daily Journal, Carrier Boys' Annual Greeting, 1897" [listed as "1a" in table of contents], 1897; 2; no. 1a
- "Ithaca Daily Journal, The Carrier's Address, 1898", 1898; 2; no. 2
- "Ithaca Daily Journal, Annual Greeting of the Carrier Boys, 1900", 1900; 2; no. 3
- "Ithaca Daily Journal, Annual Greeting of the Carrier Boys, 1901" [listed as "3a" in the table of contents], 1901; 2; no. 3a
- "Ithaca Daily Journal, Annual Greeting of the Carrier Boys, 1903", 1903; 2; no. 4
- "Ithaca Daily Journal, Annual Greeting of the Carrier Boys, 1904", 1904; 2; no. 5
- "Ithaca Daily News, Carriers' Annual New Year's Greeting, 1903", 1903; 2; no. 6
- "Ithaca Telephone Company Official List of Subscribers, no. 1, August 12, 1902", 1902; 2; no. 7
- "Ithaca Telephone Company Official List of Subscribers, no. 2, November 1, 1902" [not accounted for in table of contents], 1902; 2; no. x
- "Ithaca Telephone Company Official List of Subscribers, no. 3, January 15, 1903", 1903; 2; no. 8
- "Ithaca Telephone Company Official List of Subscribers, no.4, June 1st, 1903", 1903; 2; no. 9
- "Ithaca Telephone Company Official List of Subscribers, no.5 January 1st, 1904", 1904; 2; no. 10
- "New York and Pennsylvania Telephone and Telegraph Company Official List of Subscribers, Ithaca District, Revised February 10, 1903", 1903; 2; no. 11
- Letter addressed "To Our Patrons and the Citizens of the City of Ithaca, N.Y." by H.F. Stevens, General Manager of the New York and Pennsylvania Telephone and Telegraph Company, [n.d.]; 2; no. 12
- Sawyer, by Edward H. Rulloff [MISSING from volume; removed with FORCE], 1872; 2; no. 13
- "Memorial Sermon upon the Life and Character of Edward S. Esty, Delivered by the Rev. Asa S. Fiske, at the Special Memorial Services Held in the First Presbyterian Church, Ithaca, Sunday, October 12, 1890", 1890; 2; no. 14
- Program of coming attractions to the Lyceum, 1896; 2; no. 15
- Program for a performance by Mary Louise Clary, contralto, at the Armory, Cornell University, [1893?]; 2; no. 16
- "Contract and Specifications for Building Section _ _ _ of the Sewerage System of the City of Ithaca, New York", [n.d.]; 3; no. 1
- "Report on Plans for Sewering and Draining the City of Ithaca, N.Y.; Made to the Board of Sewer Commissioners, August 30, 1894, by Rudolph Hering, Civil Engineer" [same as 1 no. 28], 1894; 3; no. 2
- "Regulations for Admission to the Civil Service of the City of Ithaca", 1898; 3; no. 3
- "Charter of the Village of Ithaca in the County of Tompkins, Passed April 21, 1864, as Amended March 27, 1871, and May 1, 1875", 1877; 3; no. 4
- "The Water Works Question," by George Small and William Hazlitt Smith "[o]n behalf of [the Water Works] Committee," Ithaca, N.Y., Feb. 21, 1902, 1902; 3; no. 5
- Letter by the "Business Men's Association of Ithaca, N.Y.", [n.d.]; 3; no. 6
- Circular by the Ithaca Finance Committee concerning the investigation into an artesian water supply, dated March 20, 1903 [two copies], 1903; 3; no. 7
- Circular by the Ithaca Bridge Committee concerning the construction of the South Hill bridge over Six Mile Creek, dated March 7, 1895, 1895; 3; no. 8
- Menu and toast list for "The Third Annual Banquet of the Business Men's Association of Ithaca", 1900; 3; no. 9
- Menu and toast list for "The Fourth Annual Banquet of the Business Men's Association of Ithaca", 1901; 3; no. 10
- "Memorial Discourse of William Andrus, Preached by Rev. Thomas C. Strong D.D., January 16th, 1870, in the Reformed Dutch Church, of Ithaca, N.Y.", 1870; 3; no. 11
- "A Catalogue [No. 7] of Ancient and Modern Books, on Sale at the Antiquarian Book Store of H.H. Philes, Ithaca, N.Y.", Dec., 1871; 3; no. 12
- "Official Guide and Programme of the Cornell-Pennsylvania Boat Race on Cayuga Lake, Tuesday, May Thirtieth, 1899", 1899; 3; no. 13
- Program of coming attractions to the Lyceum, 1904; 3; no. 14
- Program of coming attractions to the Lyceum, 1904; 3; no. 15
- Constitution for the "Tompkins Co. Visiting Association, for the Public Institutions of Charity, the Jail, and the Department of Out-door Relief", 1874; 3; no. 16
- Charter, constitution, and by-laws for The Ithaca Children's Home, 1899; 3; no. 17
- "'Five Colonial Families: Treman, Tremaine, Truman, Mack, Dey, Board, Ayres,' by Ebenezer Mack Treman and Murray Edward Poole, D.C.L., LL.D., President of American Genealogical Society", 1901; 3; no. 18
- "Henry Bool's Apology for His Jeffersonian Anarchism", 1901; 3; no. 19
- Circular entitled "R. Heber Newton Endorses the Ideal of Anarchism", [1901?]; 3; no. 20
- Circular entitled "Individualistic Anarchism Opposed to Force" by Dr. Rudolph Steiner [excerpted from the magazine fur Literatur], [n.d.]; 3; no. 21
- Circular entitled "School of Anarchistic Economics", [n.d.]; 3; no. 22
- "Illustrated Guide Book of the Ithaca Gorge, and Its Surroundings, Edited and Compiled by William G. Johnson", 1873; 3; no. 23
- Charter and explanatory remarks of "Cascadilla Place, an Institution for the Treatment of the Sick, and the Education of Females as Physicians and Nurses," including an address by Miss S.S. Nivison, 1864; 3; no. 24
- Circular for "A New Philosophy of Creation: Darwinism Refuted, a New Basis to Evolution; Five Illustrated Lectures by Mr. E.C. Getsinger, of Detroit, Michigan", [n.d.]; 3; no. 25
- "Semi-Annual Report of the Society for the Prevention of Crime", 1883; 3; no. 26
- "Society for the Prevention of Crime, Partial Report of Work for the Past Year, Covering the Months of May, June and July, 1897", 1897; 3; no. 27
- Letter by the First National Bank, Ithaca, N.Y., announcing the retirement of the Hon. Henry B. Lord, 1901; 3; no. 28
- Letter by the Town and Gown Club with resolutions and consequent questions, dated October 31st, 1902, 1902; 3; no. 29
- Circular addressed "To the Voters of the City of Ithaca" by the Republican City Committee, concerning the candidacy of William R. Gunderman for mayor, [1901?]; 3; no. 30
- Circular by the Republican City Committee, concerning the candidacy of F.M. Rites for alderman, dated March 1, 1901, 1901; 3; no. 31
- Circular addressed "To the Voters of the City of Ithaca" by the Republican City Committee, concerning the candidacy of William R. Gunderman for mayor [same as 3 no. 30], [1901?]; 3; no. 32
- Circular entitled "Reasons why William C. Elmendorf Should be Re-elected Mayor of the City of Ithaca", [n.d.]; 3; no. 33
- Letter by the Woman's Christian Temperance Union, concerning their mission, dated November 15, 1899, 1899; 3; no. 34
- Program for the "Fourth Annual Meeting of the New York State Conference of Religion, [in] Ithaca, New York", 1903; 3; no. 35
- Tompkins County Agricultural and Horticultural Society list of premiums and regulations of the 44th Annual Fair, 1883; 3; no. 36
- Program for the "Cascadilla School Prize Contest in Declamation", 1897; 3; no. 37
- Letter addressed "To the First Congregational Society of Ithaca" by its Board of Trustees, [n.d.]; 3; no. 38
- "Manual and Directory of the First Congregational Church of Ithaca, N.Y.", 1895; 3; no. 39
- Program for the 1897 Easter services at the First Congregational Church of Ithaca, provided by Rev. William Elliot Griffis, D.D., pastor, 1897; 3; no. 40
- Church calendar for the First Presbyterian Church, Ithaca, N.Y., provided by Asa S. Fiske, D.D., pastor, Mar. 1 to Jun. 28, 1896; 3; no. 41-58
- Printed illustration of the First Presbyterian Church, [n.d.]; 3; no. 59
- Program for the "Synod of New York Twenty-Second Annual Meeting [at the] First Presbyterian Church", 1903; 3; no. 60
- Program for the "Woman's Synodical Society of Home Missions of the Synod of New York Twenty-First Annual Meeting" at the First Presbyterian Church, 1903; 3; no. 61
- "Roll and Directory of the Membership of the First Presbyterian Church", Jan., 1891; 3; no. 62
- Letter by E.P. Gilbert, chairman of "the Committee on Plans for a new building" of the First Presbyterian Church, dated January 20th, 1894, 1894; 3; no. 63
- Program of the "Services Dedicating the Church of the Unitarian Society of Ithaca, New York, May Nineteenth, 1896", 1896; 3; no. 64
- "Liberty without Invasion, Means and End of Progress," by Henry, Bool, Dec. 15, 1898; 4; no. 1
- "The Constitution, By-Laws, Officers, List of Members, Reports of Board of Managers and Treasurer of the Country Club of Ithaca, N.Y.", May, 1902; 4; no. 2
- "Constitution of the DeWitt Historical Society of Tompkins Co.", 1900; 4; no. 3
- "Rules and Regulations of the Board of Health of the City of Ithaca", 1888; 4; no. 4
- "Report of the Finance Committee of the Common Council of the City of Ithaca," dated February 21st, 1900, 1900; 4; no. 5
- List of members of the Business Men's Association of Ithaca, N.Y., [1902?]; 4; no. 6
- "Constitution and By-Laws of the Business Men's Association of Ithaca, New York", [n.d.]; 4; no. 7
- "Constitution and By-Laws of the Business Men's Association of Ithaca, New York", [n.d.]; 4; no. 8
- "Constitution and By-Laws of the Business Men's Association of Ithaca, New York", Jul., 1902; 4; no. 9
- "Constitution and By-Laws and List of Members of the Business Men's Association of Ithaca, N.Y.", Apr., 1904; 4; no. 10
- Supplement to the 1903 edition of the Business Men's Association constitution and by-laws, 1903; 4; no. 11
- Menu and toast list for the "Seventh Annual Banquet of the Ithaca Business Men's Association", 1904; 4; no. 12
- Yearly report of the Ithaca Trust Company, 1902; 4; no. 13
- Circular by Brown Brothers and Company, New York, 1902; 4; no. 14
- "Rules and Regulations for the Government of Licensed Plumbers and Layers of House Sewers in the City of Ithaca, New York", 1896; 4; no. 15
- "Prof. Schmidt's Letter of Acceptance," of the nomination by the Democratic party for the position of alderman, 1901; 4; no. 16
- "Charter, Constitution, House Rules, and Lists of Officers and Members of the Town and Gown Club, of Ithaca, New York", 1892; 4; no. 17
- "Charter, Constitution, House Rules, and Lists of Officers and Members of the Town and Gown Club, of Ithaca, New York", 1894; 4; no. 18
- "Charter, Constitution, House Rules, and Lists of Officers and Members of the Town and Gown Club, of Ithaca, New York", 1899; 4; no. 19
- Program for the "Benefit Musciale," presented by the Town and Gown Club, February 23rd, 1903, 1903; 4; no. 20
- Tompkins County Agricultural and Horticultural Society list of premiums and regulations of the 59th Annual Fair, 1898; 4; no. 21
- Advertisement with reviews of "The New Philosophy of Money," by Alfred B. Westrup, 1895; 4; no. 22
- "Young Men's Christian Association [YMCA] Hand-Book, Ithaca, New York, 1903-1904", 1903; 4; no. 23
- [Volume 5 is MISSING], [n.d.]; 5 no. x
- "Catalogue of the Loan Exhibition of the Ithaca Branch of the New York Society of Decorative Art", 1879; 6; no. 1
- Program for the Historical Dramatic Festival, April 3, 4, and 5, 1911, 1911; 6; no. 2
- "By-Laws of the Hobasco Lodge, No. 716, F. and A.M.", Nov., 1911; 6; no. 3
- "Plumbing Code: Rules and Regulations Governing Plumbing and Plumbing Fixtures, City of Ithaca, New York", 1911; 6; no. 4
- "Sanitary Code: Rules and Regulations of the Board of Health, City of Ithaca, New York", 1910; 6; no. 5
- "Schedule of Water-Rates of the City of Ithaca", 1915; 6; no. 6
- Menu and toast list for the "Fifteenth Annual Banquet of the Ithaca Business Men's Association", 1912; 6; no. 7
- Charter, constitution, and by-laws for The Ithaca Children's Home [same as 3 no. 17], 1899; 6; no. 8
- "Thirteenth Annual Catalogue of the Ithaca Conservatory of Music, Ithaca, New York", 1904; 6; no. 9
- "Constitution of the First Congregational Church, of Ithaca, New York", 1880; 6; no. 10
- Letter by Edward A. George, minister of the First Congregational Church, concerning the total number of members [not accounted for in table of contents], Mar. 29, 1913; 6; no. x
- "Report of Joint Committee on a Site for the New Hospital," written by Charles H. Hull, secretary, and Edward Meaney, M.D., chairman, May 15, 1911; 6; no. 11
- Report of the Social Service League of Ithaca, Oct., 1907; 6; no. 12
- "The Social Service League of Ithaca: Some Description of this Educational and Civic Institution", [n.d.]; 6; no. 13
- Articles of incorporation, constitution, and by-laws of the Ladies' Union Benevolent Society, 1900; 6; no. 14
- "Young Men's Christian Association [YMCA] Hand-Book, Ithaca, New York, 1903-1904" [same as 4 no. 23], 1903; 6; no. 15
- "'Report on the Hygienic and Sanitary Condition of a Public School Building' by W.E. McGown," reprinted from the Pedagogical Seminary, December, 1910, Vol. XVII, pp. 480-490, 1910; 6; no. 16
- Program for the "Sixteenth Annual Convention [of the] New York State Federation of Women's Clubs", Nov., 1910; 6; no. 17
- Guide to "Summer Resorts on or Reached by the Elmira and Cortland Division of the Lehigh Valley Railroad", [n.d.]; 6; no. 18
- "Manual of the Presbyterian Church of Ithaca, N.Y.", Jan., 1880; 7; no. 1
- Program for the Easter Day service at the First Congregational Church, provided by Rev. William Elliot Griffis, D.D., pastor, 1900; 7; no. 2
- "Loan Exhibition Catalogue Number Three's Fair", Jan., 1885; 7; no. 3
- "Telephone Guide to Ithaca and Cornell University", 1907; 7; no. 4
- Dinner and dessert menu for the "Formal Opening!" of the Ithaca Hotel, Jan. 28th, 1873, 1873; 7; no. 5
- "'A Report to Accompany Study for a System of Reservations for Ithaca, N.Y.,' by Warren H. Manning, Boston, Mass.", 1908; 7; no. 6
- Burial service of St. Augustine Commandery, No. 38, 1905; 7; no. 7
- "Farms for Sale in the Celebrated Finger Lake Region, New York State by Ithaca Realty Co.", [n.d.]; 7; no. 8
- "Constitution, By-Laws, Officers and List of Members of the Country Club of Ithaca, New York", May, 1900; 7; no. 9
- "'A Survey of the Public Healthy Situation, Ithaca, New York, 1914,' by Franz Schneider, Jr., Sanitarian", 1915; 7; no. 10
- [7 no. 11 not accounted for in table of contents nor the contents themselves; additionally, 7 no. 12-43 are not accounted for in the table of contents], [n.d.]; 7; no. 11
- "Report (No. 287) of the Commissioners for draining the Cayuga Marshes", Mar. 17, 1830; 7; no. 12
- "Report (No. 258) of the committee on the erection and division of towns and counties, on the petition of inhabitants of the town of Dryden, Tompkins county", Mar. 5, 1831; 7; no. 13
- "Report (No. 277) of the committee on the erection and division of towns and counties, on the petition of sundry inhabitants of the counties of Steuben, Tioga and Tompkins, for the erection of a new county", Mar. 16, 1831; 7; no. 14
- "Report (No. 340) of the select committee on the petition of inhabitants of the village of Ithaca, in relation to the election of constables", Mar. 26, 1831; 7; no. 15
- "Annual Report (No. 36) of Epaphras Warren, an Inspector of Beef and Pork for the county of Tompkins", Jan. 30, 1832; 7; no. 16
- "Report (No. 330) of the select committee to whom was referred the report of the Comptroller respecting the Cayuga Marshes and Swamp Lands", Apr. 12, 1831; 7; no. 17
- "Report (No. 51) of the Canal Commissioners in relation to the Cayuga Marshes"; followed by, "Report of James Geddes, Engineer, in relation to the Cayuga Marshes", Jan. 25, 1832; 7; no. 18
- "Report (No. 169) of the committee on towns and counties, on the petitions of sundry inhabitants of the counties of Steuben, Tioga and Tompkins", Feb. 17, 1832; 7; no. 19
- "Annual Report (No. 84) of E. Thayer, an Inspector of Sole Leather in and for the county of Tompkins", Jan. 26, 1832; 7; no. 20
- "Report (No. 120) of the committee on trade and manufactures, on the petition of sundry inhabitants of the county of Tompkins", Jan. 31, 1833; 7; no. 21
- "Report (No. 56) of the Committee on Roads and Bridges, on the Petitions of sundry inhabitants of the counties of Tompkins, Tioga, Broome and Chenango", Feb. 14, 1833; 7; no. 22
- "Annual Report (No. 159) of Ebenezer Thayer, an Inspector of Sole Leather for the county of Tompkins", Feb. 1, 1833; 7; no. 23
- "Annual Report (No. 73) of Philip French, an Inspector of Sole Leather for the county of Tompkins", Jan. 10, 1834; 7; no. 24
- "Annual Report (No. 72) of Hiram F. Randolph, an Inspector of Sole Leather for the county of Tompkins", Jan. 10, 1834; 7; no. 25
- "Annual Report (No. 191) of Hiram F. Randolph, an Inspector of Sole Leather for the county of Tompkins", Jan. 31, 1839; 7; no. 26
- "Report (No. 244) of the Canal Board, on the petitions of the inhabitants of the county of Tompkins, referred to them by the Hon. the Assembly", Mar. 15, 1833; 7; no. 27
- "Report (No. 267) of the committee on canals and internal improvements, on the petition of the inhabitants of the county of Tompkins", Mar. 21, 1833; 7; no. 28
- "Report (No. 348) of the Canal Board, to whom was referred by the Assembly the petition of inhabitants of the village of Ithaca, and county of Tompkins", Mar. 29, 1834; 7; no. 29
- "Report (No. 349) of the select committee on the petition of inhabitants of the counties of Cayuga and Seneca, relative to a law to prevent the killing of ducks in the Cayuga lake and outlet", Mar. 27, 1834; 7; no. 30
- "Report (No. 297) of the Canal Commissioners relative to the inlet of Cayuga Lake"; followed by estimate costs, Mar. 16, 1835; 7; no. 31
- "Annual Report (No. 98) of Hiram F. Randolph, an Inspector of Sole Leather for the county of Tompkins", Jan. 20, 1838; 7; no. 32
- "Report (No. 79) of the select committee on a resolution directing an inquiry into the propriety of abolishing public executions", Apr. 8, 1835; 7; no. 33
- "Report (No. 237) of the committee on rail-roads, on the petition of the Ithaca and Owego rail-road company", Mar. 6, 1838; 7; no. 34
- "Report (No. 111) of the Comptroller, relative to the interest of the stock issued to the Ithaca and Owego Rail-Road Company", May 4, 1839; 7; no. 35
- "Annual Report (No. 49) of Hiram F. Randolph, an Inspector of Sole Leather for the county of Tompkins", Jan. 18, 1840; 7; no. 36